To be able to manage Windows devices using Microsoft Intune,
you want to modify the environment status page so that the users,
the installation process of Windows Software or Software on the user's device,
should be a valid manage and also be controlled,
and the user should be able to see when the software is being installed.
So for example, to manage the
a remainder of speed, what you need to do is to go to your old devices and here we need to go to Windows.
So on our Windows, you can see we have the Windows enrollment.
And for the Windows enrollment page, you can see we have here what you call the enrollment status page.
So it shows up on profile installation status to use us during the files setup to just click on it.
And then you can see that the fourth installation was created for us,
but you can actually create a new one.
And so what I want to do is I want to modify the default
a remainder of speed that has already been created.
So here I'm going to go to properties, and then here on our settings I can now click a bit.
On our list, it shows apps and profile configuration progress,
which means that sometimes when you are installing this software,
when the software is being installed,
if you're under the status page here, here, by show notification,
you receive a notification at the subject about to be installed on your device, where your device should restate,
attach a software has been installed.
I think it's very important for users to be able to see this notification.
So what we need to do right now is to click yes.
And it says here you can see it's shown error when installation takes longer than specified number of minutes.
So if for example, a software has been installed on a device and it's taking a longer time,
definitely software should be taken for example between two to like 30 minutes.
But if it's taking system is definitely you want to actually show an error.
Or if you think there are software which is a longer time to install,
we can't really change these to like 90 minutes.
So if your customer said when time limits or error of course,
you can say you see at this moment says yes,
set up should not be completely striking or contact your supports.
For help, you can just add, for example, email address info at kelv global.com.
So for example, you can add an email address or you can modify the tests.
So that users can actually see a miss it and send an email to the IT Hub does.
Or definitely, these are already know how to contact the IT Hub that's without you putting your email address.
And also you can see turn on local collection and diagnostics page for any of this.
With means that during the installation process of a specific software,
there's going to be a log created so that you need to when something goes wrong.
You should be able to actually check that log and analyze the installation process and know
that's sadly where the installation feels and know why it feels.
And here it says only short-speed device provision by out of the browser.
Of course, you have to want to put out a yes.
And also block device use until all apps and profiles are installed.
Definitely yes, if, for example, you allow you want to allow.
So sometimes you want to configure your profile account or configuration profile to say,
okay, around the user to be able to use this device, if the fake apps are installed
or if special requirements are meant.
So here you can see that is actually turn on.
And also you want to see that allow user to reset the device if installation or of course,
this is a little less for you to see what sometimes I think it's better to say no,
because the user may just set the devices.
Allow users to use the device if installation or cause.
I want to put that to a yes.
So I just be able to still use the device if there's an error during installation.
Block device use on to required apps are installed if they are assigned to the
without device. We're going to leave that to adjust all and then we're going to save review.
And here you can see what we just configured.
And right now we can now click save.
And at this moment, you can see it says assignments include groups to all devices.
Which means that this is going to be applied to all your devices.
And that's actually recognized in Microsoft in June.